mynewsla.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy - MyNewsLA.com

MyNewsLA.com and its owner CalNews Inc. recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about our readers and advertisers. In adopting this privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using information with your reasonable expectations of privacy.

MyNewsLA.com does not collect personally identifying information about individuals, except when specifically and knowingly provided by those individuals, such as to subscribe to our email newsletters, or to register for a contest or promotion.

Web servers hosting MyNewsLA.com automatically collect anonymous information about which pages you visit, your browser type, IP address,  domain name, interaction with advertising and other data. This is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for traffic audits. We also provide this information about our users on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our advertisers.

MyNewsLA.com collects this information by saving a data “cookie” to the browser cache of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. A cookie can be used to tell when your computer has contacted a website. We use the information  track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site without compromising privacy. For example, cookies are used to ensure that you don’t see the same ad too many times.

Advertising that is part of a network advertising service that collects information about a consumer’s online activities on a website over time and across different websites is identified by a small Ad Choices symbol. This symbol is part of the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You can click the symbol for information about why and how you are receiving a particular ad, and the effect of your choice to allow or not allow tracking for targeted ads. For more information see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Note that due to inconsistent and changing technology we cannot always honor a browser’s Do Not Track signal. You may opt-out of a network advertising service ad by changing your cookie settings.

If you provide your email address in order to receive email newsletters and alerts, we may from time to time send you information about MyNewsLA.com products and services, but will not do so on behalf of third parties. You may unsubscribe at anytime via the link at the bottom of each email message, or by contacting our office by [email](mailto:info@mynewsla.com), phone or U.S. mail.

Our comments feature is provided in partnership with Facebook and privacy is covered by that company’s policy. You should also be aware that it you voluntarily disclose personal information in comments, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages.

If we offer contests or promotions on the site, you may be required to provide information such as your telephone number and address in order to participate. The exact rules may vary in each case but the specific rules for any contest will state how that information may be used.

Beyond collection of your email address for newsletters and alerts, and possibly other information for contests and promotions, MyNewsLA.com will not request personal information. Any personal information provided will not be shared with third parties, except as operationally necessary for website hosting, or if required by law.

We reserve the right to fully use, disclose and process any non-personal information collected from you in any manner and any information you make public via our website

Note that MyNewsLA.com does not control the privacy policies of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks.

_Special Note to Parents:_ We encourage you to get involved with your children’s online use and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating. If we become aware that personal information from a child under 13 has been collected without a parent or guardian’s consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to remove such information from our database.

We often update and develop new services, features, activities and content from time to time and will need to change our privacy policy accordingly. We will provide notice via postings on our website, and we will also post the date when the privacy policy was last updated and effective. Your continued use of our website constitutes your acceptance of any changes in our privacy policy, except where further steps are required by applicable law.

_Updated and effective February 1, 2015_

Privacy Policy was last modified:  February 1st, 2015 by
